Guide to the Montana Legislature (66th: 2019) records, 2019 2018-2019
Montana Historical Society, Research Center Archives
- Senate, 2018-2019
  - Standing Committee Minutes, 2018-2019
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 February 19-26 (Box Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 March 8-22 (Box Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 March 25 (Box Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 March 26 (Box Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 March 28-29 (Box Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 April 2-3 (Box Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 April 5-9 (Box Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 April 10-12 (Box Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Finance and Claims, 2019 April 12-13 (Box Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Fish and Game, 2019 January 8 - February 5 (Box Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Fish and Game, 2019 February 7-21 (Box Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Fish and Game, 2019 February 26 - March 19 (Box Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Fish and Game - March 14 Exhibit 1 (Content of media has been printed and is in original folder.) (Box Oversize Box 1)
    - Fish and Game, 2019 March 21 - April 4 (Box Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Fish and Game, 2019 April 9-24 (Box Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Highways and Transportation, 2019 January 8-15 (Box Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Highways and Transportation, 2019 January 17-29 (Box Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Highways and Transportation, 2019 January 31 - February 12 (Box Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Highways and Transportation, 2019 February 14 - March 12 (Box Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Highways and Transportation, 2019 March 14 - April 4 (Box Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Highways and Transportation, 2019 April 9-18 (Box Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Judiciary, 2019 January 9-10 (Box Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Judiciary, 2019 January 11-22 (Box Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Judiciary, 2019 January 23-29 (Box Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Judiciary, 2019 January 30 - February 5 (Box Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 6-12 (Box Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 13-14 (Box Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 15-21 (Box Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Judiciary, 2019 February 22-27 (Box Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Judiciary - February 22 Exhibit 1 (Ask archivist for assistance) (Box Oversize Box 1)
    - Judiciary, 2019 March 8-14 (Box Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Judiciary, 2019 March 15-21 (Box Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Judiciary, 2019 March 22-26 (Box Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Judiciary, 2019 March 27-29 (Box Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Judiciary, 2019 April 2-5 (Box Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Judiciary, 2019 April 9-11 (Box Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Judiciary, 2019 April 12-25 (Box Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Local Government, 2019 January 9-30 (Box Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Local Government, 2019 February 11-15 (Box Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Local Government, 2019 February 18-25 (Box Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Local Government, 2019 March 11-27 (Box Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Local Government, 2019 April 3-10 (Box Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 January 9-14 (Box Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 January 16-28 (Box Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Natural Resources - January 16 Exhibit 2 (Box Oversize Box 1)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 January 30 - February 18 (Box Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 February 20-25 (Box Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 March 11-20 (Box Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 March 22 - April 8 (Box Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources, 2019 April 10-17 (Box Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 January 9-16 (Box Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 January 23-28 (Box Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 January 30 - February 13 (Box Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 February 18 (Box Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 February 20-26 (Box Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 March 11-15 (Box Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 March 18 (Box Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 March 18 (Box Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 March 18 (Box Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 March 18 (Box Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 March 20-27 (Box Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 April 1-5 (Box Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 April 8-10 (Box Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Public Health, Welfare, and Safety, 2019 April 12-24 (Box Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Rules, 2018 December 4 (Box Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Rules, 2019 January 9-21 (Box Box 20, Folder 7)
    - State Administration, 2019 January 9-21 (Box Box 20, Folder 8)
    - State Administration, 2019 January 23 - February 6 (Box Box 20, Folder 9)
    - State Administration, 2019 February 11-18 (Box Box 20, Folder 10)
    - State Administration, 2019 February 20 - March 11 (Box Box 20, Folder 11)
    - State Administration, 2019 March 13-20 (Box Box 20, Folder 12)
    - State Administration, 2019 March 22 -April 4 (Box Box 20, Folder 13)
    - State Administration, 2019 April 3-17 (Box Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 9-17 (Box Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 22 (Box Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 22 (Box Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 22 (Box Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 23-31 (Box Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Taxation, 2019 January 31 - February 13 (Box Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Taxation, 2019 February 14-19 (Box Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Taxation, 2019 February 20-25 (Box Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Taxation, 2019 February 26 - March 14 (Box Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Taxation, 2019 March 15-21 (Box Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Taxation, 2019 March 22-26 (Box Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Taxation, 2019 March 27 - April 5 (Box Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Taxation, 2019 April 9-11 (Box Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Bills, 2019
    - SB 1 - SB 11, 2019 (Box Box 21, Folder 10)
    - SB 12 - SB 23, 2019 (Box Box 21, Folder 11)
    - SB 24 - SB 30, 2019 (Box Box 21, Folder 12)
    - SB 31 - SB 38, 2019 (Box Box 21, Folder 13)
    - SB 39 -SB 46, 2019 (Box Box 21, Folder 14)
    - SB 47 - SB 51, 2019 (Box Box 21, Folder 15)
    - SB 52 - SB 55, 2019 (Box Box 21, Folder 16)
    - SB 56 - SB 59, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 1)
    - SB 60 - SB 63, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 2)
    - SB 64 - SB 65, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 3)
    - SB 66 - SB 75, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 4)
    - SB 76 - SB 88, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 5)
    - SB 89 - SB 106, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 6)
    - SB 108 - SB 124, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 7)
    - SB 125 - SB 137, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 8)
    - SB 138 - SB 150, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 9)
    - SB 151 - SB 158, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 10)
    - SB 159 - SB 168, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 11)
    - SB 169 - SB 183, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 12)
    - SB 184 - SB 199, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 13)
    - SB 200 - SB 202, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 14)
    - SB 203 - SB 214, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 15)
    - SB 215 - SB 224, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 16)
    - SB 225, 2019 (Box Box 22, Folder 17)
    - SB 226 - SB 239, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 1)
    - SB 240 - SB 252, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 2)
    - SB 253 - SB 259, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 3)
    - SB 260 - SB 265, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 4)
    - SB 266 - SB 269, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 5)
    - SB 270 - SB 276, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 6)
    - SB 277 - SB 292, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 7)
    - SB 293 - SB 302, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 8)
    - SB 303 - SB 313, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 9)
    - SB 314 - SB 324, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 10)
    - SB 325, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 11)
    - SB 326 - SB 330, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 12)
    - SB 331 - SB 338, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 13)
    - SB 339 - SB 345, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 14)
    - SB 346 - SB 348, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 15)
    - SB 350 - SB 358, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 16)
    - SB 359 - SB 366, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Resolutions, 2019
    - SR 1 - SR 21, 2019 (Box Box 23, Folder 18)
    - SR 22 - SR 65, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Joint Resolutions, 2019
    - SJ 1 - SJ 12, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 2)
    - SJ 13 - SJ 32, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Journals, 2019
    - Day 1 - 19, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Day 20 - 33, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Day 34 - 43, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Day 44 - 66, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Day 67 - 75, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Day 76 - 80, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Day 81 - 87, 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 10)
- Miscellany, 2019
  - Memorials B-H (Barnhart, Beverly H.; Bartlett, Janet Susan; Bengtson, Esther G.; Brooke, Vivian Morgan; Curtiss, Aubyn; Eck, Dorothy; Elliott, Roger H.; Getz, Dennis; Gibson, Carol; Haines, Richard E. "Dick"; Hargrove, Don), 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Memorials J-Z (Johnson, Royal Calvin; Kimberley, Bervyl C.; Knapp, Roger Rance; Lockrem, Lloyd D. "Sonny" Jr.; Lynch, John Daniel "J.D."; McOmber, Willis "Gordon"; Mohl, Arnold "Arnie"; Mueller, Glenn; Price, Jean Louise; Ringling, Paul; Sales, Walter; Southworth, Clarice Branger Schrumpf; Spaeth, Gary L.; Waddill, Durward C. "Butch"; Waterman, Mignon; Zook, Thomas Frederick), 2019 (Box Box 24, Folder 12)